<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<odoo>
    <template id="addendum_pdf_id_print">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                <div class="article o_report_layout_standard" t-att-data-oe-model="doc and doc._name"
                     t-att-data-oe-id="doc and doc.id">
                    <t t-call="property.custom_session_header_footer"/>
                    <div class="page" style=" padding-top: 40px; font-size:14px">
                        <span>This Addendum shall form part of the Tenancy Contract No; _____________________ and must
                            be read in conjunction with the Contract between the “Landlord” __________________________
                            (LL) “Tenant” ________________________________ (TT).
                        </span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>The “Premises” shall mean the property including gardens, common communal entrances
                            facilities. “Fixtures, Furnishings and Fittings” shall mean all that is now in or on the
                            Premises.
                        </span>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <span>The TT and LL agree as follows:</span>
                        <div style=" padding-top: 3px; width:100%;" class="row">
                            <table>
                                <tr class="table table-md">
                                    <td width="40%" style="font-size:12px">
                                        <strong>1 Security Deposit</strong>
                                        <br/>
                                        <!--                                         <p class="text-justify" style="padding-left:30px"> -->
                                        <p class="text-justify">
                                            1.1 The Tenant has paid AED _______/-
                                            <br/>
                                            (________________________) with 1 st year contract as a security Deposit.
                                            This will be refunded to the Tenant when vacating, subject to the Premises
                                            being left in a satisfactory condition as to when the apartment was handed
                                            over to the Tenant and Tenant and receipts of all paid bills being given to
                                            The Landlord.
                                            <br/>
                                            1.2 If any damages are formed or necessary repair paint or cleaning works
                                            are required the LL reserves the right to deduct the cost of such expenses
                                            from TT’s security deposit subject to normal wear and tear.
                                            <br/>
                                        </p>
                                        <span>
                                            <strong>2 Use of Premises</strong>
                                        </span>
                                        <br/>
                                        <p>
                                            2.1 It is understood that the TT will use the Premises for residential
                                            purposes only and the TT shall not use the Premises to carry out any
                                            profession, trade or business whatsoever.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.2 The TT is not allowed to assign, sublet or lease the property to any
                                            third party.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.3 The TT shall not make any addition or alteration to the Premises without
                                            the written consent of the LL.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.4 The erection of any board or notice visible from outside of the property
                                            advertising any profession, trade, business, goods or service is prohibited.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.5 Rules of Association shall apply as set by the developer.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.6 The TT shall not do or permit any act that may cause injury, damage,
                                            nuisance or annoyance to a neighbouring property or person and shall respect
                                            any community by laws.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.7 The Premises shall not be used for any illegal or immoral purpose in
                                            contravention of any emirate regulation or by law.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.8 The keeping of any pets on the Premises must be with prior consent of
                                            the LL. As per the community rules “pets are not allowed” and if any such
                                            violation is reported by the community management, the TT shall rectify this
                                            immediately.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.9 It is understood that the municipality reserve the right to evict
                                            non-sharing families.
                                            <br/>
                                            2.10 The TT shall not glue carpet or wooden grippers to the floor surfaces.
                                            <br/>
                                        </p>
                                        <span>
                                            <strong>3 Terms of Payment</strong>
                                        </span>
                                        <br/>
                                        3.1 The Tenant shall pay the rent annually in advance in _ (_____) Cheques
                                        Instalments.
                                        <br/>
                                        3.2 The TT understands that non-clearance of a cheque is unlawful, and they
                                        shall be charged AED 500 for each bounced cheque.
                                        <br/>
                                        <span>
                                            <strong>4 Interior Furnishing</strong>
                                        </span>
                                        <br/>
                                        4.1 The TT shall not remove at any time during or after the tenancy any item of
                                        fixtures, furnishings and fittings.
                                        <br/>
                                        4.2 Insuring the contents of the property is the responsibility of the TT.
                                        <br/>
                                        <span>
                                            <strong>5 Reinstatement/ Reconstruction</strong>
                                        </span>
                                        <br/>
                                        5.1 By the end of this Tenancy Contract, the TT will be responsible for
                                        reinstatement or reconstruction of any areas/parts/furniture removed, damaged
                                        (other than normal wear tear), or change inside of the Premises to the
                                        Landlord’s Satisfaction.
                                        <br/>
                                        5.2 Upon vacation of the Premises, the LL is not responsible for reimbursing any
                                        money spent by the TT on the upgrading of the Premises.
                                        <br/>
                                        5.3 The TT agrees to make good, repair or cover replacement cost any item
                                        damaged by the TT, his family or guests.
                                    </td>
                                    <td width="40%" style="font-size:12px;">
                                        <strong>6 Maintenance and Utilities</strong>
                                        <br/>
                                        6.1 The TT will keep the interior of the Premises and fixtures and fittings
                                        (including paint and decorations and appliances) in good condition during the
                                        tenancy.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.2 The TT undertakes to immediately notify the LL in the event of fire, flood
                                        or any other incident involving the Premises or upon the discovery of any damage
                                        or fault in the Premises requiring repair or attention.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.3 The Tenant is responsible for all minor maintenance repairs upto AED 500
                                        per Invoice or per visit of service provider to the premises including
                                        electrical, plumbing, air-conditioning servicing, gas, thermostat etc, any cost
                                        above AED 500 per Invoice or per visit of service provider will be the
                                        responsibility of LL (This does not include any upgradation to the unit or any
                                        consumables like lights , wooden flooring, wall paper, etc).
                                        <br/>
                                        6.4 The TT shall be responsible for all utility consumption charges that are
                                        directly billed to the TT during the tenancy, including, DEWA, Cooling charges,
                                        Municipality Taxes, telephone, television and internet charges as well as any
                                        new government charges that may be levied.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.5 Community Service charges are the responsibility of the LL.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.6 The TT shall be responsible for the maintenance and associated charges for
                                        the lawns, shrubs and trees if present within the Premises.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.7 Positive Properties has no responsibility towards any maintenance repairs
                                        and or management unless otherwise specified or employed to do so by either
                                        party.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.8 At the time of vacating the Premises, the TT will pay up and produce the
                                        receipts for the final DEWA, AC and utility bills.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.9 The TT shall permit the LL or his representative access to the Premises
                                        (upon reasonable notice) for the purpose of repairing snags or inspecting the
                                        Premises.
                                        <br/>
                                        6.10
                                        <span style="color:red">The TT responsibility to register the Ejari contract and
                                            cancel the Ejari contract at the end of the Tenancy and provide proof of
                                            cancellation.
                                        </span>
                                        <br/>
                                        <strong>7 End of Tenancy</strong>
                                        <br/>
                                        7.1 This tenancy contract can be renewed after one year, subject to the TT
                                        giving the LL at least 90 days’ notice, in writing, prior to the expiry date and
                                        the LL accepting, in writing.
                                        <br/>
                                        7.2 In the event that the LL wishes the TT to vacate the Premises for the
                                        purpose of moving in or selling the property, the LL should notify the TT, in
                                        writing, stamped by the courts and notary public/Fed EX’d twelve months prior to
                                        the expiry of the contract and in line with RERA guidelines.
                                        <br/>
                                        7.3 IIn the event of the LL and TT extending the Tenancy for a further year a
                                        rent review shall take place according to the current RERA rental index
                                        calculator.
                                        <br/>
                                        7.4 In the event of the TT and LL agreeing to renew the Tenancy Contract,
                                        Positive Properties will charge an administration fee of AED 500 + VAT to draw
                                        up a new Tenancy Contract payable by the TT.
                                        <br/>
                                        7.5 If the TT does not wish to extend the tenancy, he agrees to give access in
                                        the last 30 days of the tenancy to show prospective new tenants, being given at
                                        least one day’s notice for viewings
                                        <br/>
                                        7.6 The TT shall clean the Premises and return it as it was handed over to the
                                        TT at the time of occupying it.
                                        <br/>
                                        7.7 The TT agrees to re-paint the apartment prior to vacating the Premises or
                                        pay the LL for the cost of such re-painting.
                                        <br/>
                                        7.8 In the event that the TT wishes to vacate the Premises prior to the expiry
                                        of the contract, the TT shall give 2 months’ written notice and pay a penalty
                                        equivalent to Two month’s rent and the LL shall reimburse the balance of the
                                        rent and the security deposit.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                    <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                </div>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
    <template id="custom_session_header_footer">
        <t t-set="company" t-value="user.company_id"/>
        <div class="header first-page">
            <!--             <div style="text-align: center;"> -->
            <!--                 <img src='/credit_application/static/description/logo2.jpg' style="height:270px; width:500px;"/> -->
            <!--             </div> -->
        </div>
        <div class="footer">
            <table class="table table-borderless table-sm" style="table-layout: fixed; width: 100%; font-size:13px;">
                <tr>
                    <td>
                        <hr style="border-top: 1px solid black; width:150px;"/>
                        <span style="padding-left:20px">
                            <strong>Landlord Signature</strong>
                        </span>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <hr style="border-top: 1px solid black; width:150px;"/>
                        <span style="padding-left:50px">
                            <strong>Witness</strong>
                        </span>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <hr style="border-top: 1px solid black; width:150px;"/>
                        <span style="padding-left:30px">
                            <strong>Tenant Signature</strong>
                        </span>
                    </td>
                    <td>
                        <hr style="border-top: 1px solid black; width:150px;"/>
                        <span style="padding-left:50px">
                            <strong>Witness</strong>
                        </span>
                    </td>
                </tr>
            </table>
        </div>
    </template>
</odoo>